<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Resume Blog</title>
        <link>https://everking.github.io/resume/blog</link>
        <description>Resume Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <link>https://everking.github.io/resume/blog/welcome</link>
            <guid>welcome</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Welcome to my website, which I'm using to review,]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to my website, which I'm using to review,
enhance and showcase my front-end skills.</p><p>However, as you can see in my <a href="/resume/">resume</a>, I definitely
do a lot more than front-end develpment.</p><p>I started my career writing firmware code using assembler language
that was literally burned into the chip to deploy to handheld computer.</p><p>Since then, I'd beed working on databases, desktop applications,
systems management coding, and literally all aspects of web development.</p><p>Essentially, I do what needs to be done. </p><p>I go where I'm needed.</p><p>It doesn't mean that I don't care where I go or what I do. </p><p>It's quite the opposite.</p><p>It's just that, I seem to have this knack on making un-intesting
things interesting, through curiousity and creativity. </p><p>For example, we wanted to send customized Christmas cards
to family and friends. I wrote code in VB for Applications to
tell CorelDraw to export images with their names.</p><p>In Chevron, when I'm on a "graveyard" shift, I could have just
done my usual checklist, monitoring servers, doing walkthroughs,
etc. Instead, during quiet times and there are a lot of those,
I wrote code creating flash (flex) based dashboard shown on TVs.</p><p>Basically. I love coding.</p><p>I love technology. </p><p>Others have painting, reading or sports to do at their liesure time.
I have technology.</p><p>I'm creative and persistent enough that I'm able to find ways
to do it in a lot of very different ways.</p><p>By the way, I pride myself as an artist
as well, so, I try to sprinkle that wheneveer there's an
opportunity to do so. This website is an excellent example.</p><p>Thank you for taking the time to read this blog post.</p><p>Cheers!</p>]]></content:encoded>
            <category>eric-deguzman</category>
            <category>reactjs</category>
            <category>docusaurus</category>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>